// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which extinguishes the fire of flammable liquids?",
  //  immg:"img1",
    answer: "CO2",
    options: [
      "Water",
      "Air",
      "CO2",
      "Oil"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the type of chisel?",
    immg:"img2",
    answer: "Diamond Point",
    options: [
      "Flat",
      "Cross Cut",
      "Half round",
      "Diamond Point"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which materials are used to make mallets?",
   
    answer: "Wood, rubber",
    options: [
      "Wood, cast iron",
      "Wood, rubber",
      "Rubber, brass",
      "Wood, brass"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is tje angle marked as X in sheet metal V notch?",
    immg:"img4",
    answer: "90o",
    options: [
      "90o",
      "60o",
      "45o",
      "30o"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which tool is used for bending, seaming and forming of sheet metal?",
    //immg:"img2",
    answer: "Stakes",
    options: [
      "Bench vice",
      "Hand Vice",
      "Stakes",
      "Shear"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the tool used for bending sheet metal?",
    immg:"img6",
    answer: "Blow horn stake",
    options: [
      "Bevel edged square stake",
      "Blow horn stake",
      "Hatchet stake",
      "Square stake"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the name of part marked as X in snips?",
    immg:"img7",
    answer: "Stops",
    options: [
      "Handle",
      "Black",
      "Stops",
      "Bolt"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the name of the soldering tool?",
    immg:"img8",
    answer: "Soldering gun",
    options: [
      "Blow lamp",
      "Pot and ladle",
      "Soldering gun",
      "Soldering iron"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which tool is ued for bending long sheet metal?",
   // immg:"img8",
    answer: "Folding bar",
    options: [
      "Folding bar",
      "Bench Vice",
      "Hand Vice",
      "Shear"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which tool is used for tightening the odd size bolts and nuts?",
   // immg:"img8",
    answer: "Adjustable spanner",
    options: [
      "Socket set",
      "Nose pliers",
      "Ring spanner",
      "Adjustable spanner"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which tool is uded for trimming the edges of a sheet metal cylinder?",
   // immg:"img8",
    answer: "Bent snips",
    options: [
      "Straight snips",
      "Bent snips",
      "Tube cutter",
      "Scissors"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is smoothering in fire extingusishing?",
   // immg:"img8",
    answer: "Cutting off oxygen supply to fire",
    options: [
      "Pouring of CTC",
      "Flashing with dry powder",
      "Use water to lower temperature",
      "Cutting off oxygen supply to fire"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What is starving in extingushing the fire?",
   // immg:"img8",
    answer: "Removal of fuel",
    options: [
      "Adding fuel",
      "Removal of fuel",
      "Clearing the hazards",
      "Stop the supply of oxygen"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What is the material composition of a Tin mans solder?",
   // immg:"img8",
    answer: "50% Tin 50% Lead",
    options: [
      "50% Tin 50% Zinc",
      "50% Tin 50% Lead",
      "50% Zinc 50% lead",
      "50% Tin 50% Bronze"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the name of part marked as X in outside micrometer?",
    immg:"img15",
    answer: "Barrel",
    options: [
      "Barrel",
      "Spindle",
      "Lock nut",
      "Steel frame"
    ]
  },
       {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Which is the point angle of a twist drill used for zinc alloy?",
   // immg:"img15",
    answer: "118o",
    options: [
      "90o",
      "100o",
      "118o",
      "125o"
    ]
  },
       {
    numb: 17,
    question: "What is the angle of the itp of centre punch?",
   // immg:"img15",
    answer: "90o",
    options: [
      "30o",
      "60o",
      "90o",
      "125o"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which file is used for filing wood?",
   // immg:"img15",
    answer: "Smooth file",
    options: [
      "Double cut file",
      "Single cut file",
      "Smooth file",
      "Rasp cut file"
    ]
  },

     {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Which operation is in progress?",
    immg:"img19",
    answer: "Tapping",
    options: [
      "Reaming",
      "Marking",
      "Tapping",
      "Drilling"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which medium isused to extiguish Class-A fire?",
    //immg:"img19",
    answer: "Water",
    options: [
      "CO2",
      "Foam",
      "Water",
      "Dry powder"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 21,
    question: "What is the use of the tool in bevelling a drilled hole on job?",
    immg:"img21",
    answer: "Counter Sinking",
    options: [
      "Drilling",
      "Reaming",
      "Counter Sinking",
      "Counter boring"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Which material is used to clean oil and grease on the floor?",
   // immg:"img21",
    answer: "Saw Dust",
    options: [
      "Cotton Waste",
      "Saw Dust",
      "Water",
      "Air"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 23,
    question: "What is the least count of vernier calipers?",
    immg:"img23",
    answer: "0.02",
    options: [
      "0.01",
      "0.02",
      "0.10",
      "0.20"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 24,
    question: "Which operation is progressed on the job?",
    immg:"img24",
    answer: "Reaming",
    options: [
      "Drilling",
      "Marking",
      "Tapping",
      "Reaming"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Which operation is progress by snips?",
    immg:"img25",
    answer: "Trimming cylinder",
    options: [
      "Straight cutting",
      "Steel tube cutting",
      "Trimming cylinder",
      "Copper tube cutting"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Which operation is in progress?",
    immg:"img26",
    answer: "Punching",
    options: [
      "Cutting",
      "Drilling",
      "Marking",
      "Punching"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 27,
    question: "What is the name of part marked as X in surface gauge?",
    immg:"img27",
    answer: "Snug",
    options: [
      "Nut",
      "Snug",
      "Base",
      "Spindle"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
